Keep your friends close and your enemies dead.
Fast Charlie is a action, crime, drama film directed by Phillip Noyce.
When his aging mob boss is whacked, Charlie Swift, a loyal friend and hired gun,
will stop at nothing to destroy the upcoming crew that took him out.
Charlie Swift, played by Pierce Brosnan.
Marcie Kramer, played by Morena Baccarin.
Stan Mullen, played by James Caan.
Beggar, played by Gbenga Akinnagbe.
Benny, played by Toby Huss.
Sal, played by Fredric Lehne.
Fast Charlie is a 2023 American action thriller film directed by Phillip Noyce and written
by Richard Wenk, based on the 2001 novel Gun Monkeys by Victor Gischler.
It stars Pierce Brosnan, Morena Baccarin and James Caan in his final film role.
It premiered at the 2023 Mill Valley Film Festival on October 7, 2023.
The film was released in select theatres and
video on demand on December 8, 2023.
The tone is emotional.